<resources>
    <string name="common_string_appname">Kore</string>
    <string name="common_string_next">Next</string>
    <string name="common_string_extended">Extended</string>
    <string name="common_string_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="common_string_change">Change</string>
    <string name="common_string_close">Close</string>

    <string name="setuplayout_string_help">Click on the ❓ for mor details</string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_hellowelcome">Hello and welcome</string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_smallexplanaition">
        To this awesome App!\n
        You\'re on the right way to safely keep your most important things (the access data to all of your accounts)
        right next to you in your pocket.\n
        This App lets you do this in a nice and easy way. I (the developer) hope you enjoy this app the little time you
        going to use it.\n
        In the next step you have to setup your master password so don\'t wait and hit "setup"
    </string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_setmasterpassword">Set your master password</string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_enterpassword">Enter your password</string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_repeatpassword">Repeat your password</string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_exportheader">So you\'re an expert…!</string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_helpextended">To get help by choosing the right values click the ?-button</string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_pimhelp">If you don\'t enter a PIM it will keep the calculated.</string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_calcpim">Your calculated PIM: ${_pim_}</string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_enterpim">Enter your PIM</string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_repeatpim">Repeat your PIM</string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_extendedtext">
        In this view you can see your password and the correlating PIM. You can keep the PIM or change it, but be
        careful!
    </string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_passwordhelp">
        To get help by choosing the right password click the ❓
    </string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_cancelextended">No, get me out!</string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_hintextended">Uhh, an expert coming along!</string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_extenedcontinue">Yes, continue</string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_setuptext">Setup</string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_enteredpimsdontmatch">The entered PIMs don\'t match!</string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_pimhint">
        Your entered PIM seems to be a bit low! You should use a 5 digit number between 20000 and 30000. Check help if
        you\'re not sure.
    </string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_keeppim">Keep PIM</string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_pimhinthigh">
        Your entered PIM seems to be a bit high! If you choose a high PIM the app may slow down significantly. Check
        help if you\'re not sure.
    </string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_passwordsdontmatch">Passwords don\'t match!</string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_continueanyway">Continue anyway</string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_weakpasswordhint">
        Your password doesn\'t seem to be safe enough! Check help for more information.
    </string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_setuperror">
        Error during setup. Please try again. If it still fails, please select another password.
    </string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_helptext1">
        In this app you can easily store all of your passwords. You may know this because the small description from
        this app and the PlayStore site already told you.
    </string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_helptext2">
        To store your passwords this app uses an 256bit encrypted database which is state of the art of encrypting
        files.
    </string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_helptext3">
        Here may be some more text but I\'m to lazy to write even more text.
    </string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_helpheader">Help!</string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_helppassword1">First of all you have to ask this few questions:\n\t1.\tIs the
        password \"burtforcable\". This means can it be guessed by trying all possibilities. This happens if your
        password has less than 8 characters and has not much diversity. (This is what called entropy, which is the
        little view beneath the password input, which will be there some time in the future).\n
        \t2.\tMay your password appear in some password dictionaries. These dictionaries are leaked password databases
        from some companies which got hacked by some bad guys. If your password is pretty simple it may appear in one of
        these dictionaries and can be guessed easily.
    </string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_helppassword2">
        So choosing \"password\" as password is pretty bad. Also \"password123\" is not good.
    </string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_helppassword3">
        Now how to choose a good password? First way is to choose three to four random words which (and this is
        important) are not so common to speak or write. If you choose a password like this your password is long enough
        not to be brutforced and is not this likely to be found in a dictionary.\nSounds good, doesn\'t it?
    </string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_helppassword4">
        To get an even better password (and annoy almost everyone) just put an underscore (\"_\") right in the middle
        of your word sequence. Or an ampersand (\"&amp;\") right in the middle of a
        word like \"horse\" becomes \"ho&amp;rse\".
    </string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_helppassword5">
        And the second way is the old fashioned way to choose a password. Choose randomly more (a lot more) than 8 upper
        and lower case letters, some digits and special characters. This way your password is hard to brutforce and the
        possibility to find this in a password dictionary is pretty low.\n
        Of course these passwords are hard to remember, so don\'t forget it.
    </string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_helpsubheader">
        So this little help is supposed to help you to find the right password.
    </string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_helpextended1">
        Because you are an expert you probably know how to choose a password. If you don\'t know here\'s the TL;DR
        version:\n\t1.\tChoose a password with a high entropy. So many different characters in your password so it
        cannot be brutforced easily.\n\t2.\tYour password should be unique so it doesn\'t appear in any password
        dictionary. If you choose words as password, select 4 random uncommon words and put a special character like
        &amp; or an underscore \'_\' somewhere in your password.
    </string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_helpextended2">
        So what\'s this PIM?\nPIM stands for \"Personal Iterations Multiplier\" and is a simple number. This number is
        used by the generation for the final password to encrypt the database. So it\'s the number of iterations used
        for the key derivation.
    </string>
    <string name="setuplayout_string_helpextended3">
        If you choose your own PIM it should be a five digit number between 20,000 and 30,000. Though the developer of
        the encrypted database library says on his website if a password is set the PIM should be about 10000. But to
        provide more security the generated and your selected PIM should be a little bit higher. But the PIM shouldn\'t
        be to high because the login and setup will take ages and you won\'t have a good experience and using the app
        will be annoying.
    </string>
    <string name="loginlayout_string_password">Password</string>
</resources>
